翻译: 马西萝卜 威力 一个椰子
Peralta 你是在吃意式三明治当早餐吗
Peralta are you eating an Italian sub for breakfast?
对啊 只不过Amy说我应该多吃蔬菜
I am. But Amy said I should eat more veges
校对: 番茄滚滚
所以我多加了点辣椒
so I got extra peperoncinos.
太机智了
Smart.
后期: 池三斗
嘿 不好意思
Uh, excuse me.
你能当心点吗
You need to watch yourself.
真抱歉
I'm sorry...
条子
cop.
压制: 怪查理
淡定
All right,
大家保持淡定
let's everybody just stay calm here.
不然呢
Or what?
你要因为跳舞逮捕我吗
Are you gonna arrest me for dancing?
你叫那跳舞
You call that dancing?
这才是跳舞
This is dancing.
现在什么状况
What is happening?
我在缓和紧张局势
I'm defusing the situation.
哇 热舞中的警监
Whoa... dancing captain.
我得拍下这足以铭记一生的画面
Must capture image of a lifetime!
为什么我的手机老是死机
Oh, why is my phone always dead?
我花了13美元买的它
I paid $13 for it.
别担心 Jakey 有我呢
Don't worry, Jakey. I got it.
哦
Okay. Oh!
做黄油搞得我手上
Oh, my hands are covered in butter
全是黄油
from making butter.
拿到了
I'm on it!
一定要录下来 一定要啊
Must record, must record!
相机准备好了
Camera on.
搞定 来吧
All right. Here we go.
热舞结束
Dancing over.
局势缓和
Situation defused.
不
No!
神烦警探
第三季 第十一集
电波诚译
Jakey
Jakey!
嘿
Hey!
你们俩是围着一条围巾吗
Are you guys wearing one scarf?
对啊 Charles今天早上忘记带他的了
Yep, Charles forgot his this morning.
其实还蛮浪漫的
It's actually quite romantic.
我觉得他肯定是故意的
I think he did it on purpose.
这么说吧
Uh, let's just say,
我就是故意的
I definitely did it on purpose.
现在 让我旋转起来 宝贝
Now, twirl me, darling!
来了 小山芋
You got it, sweet potato.
我无法离开你
Ah, I can't get away from you.
好了 你们俩太恩爱了
All right, you guys are adorable.
医生说你的子宫状况怎么样
Tell me everything the doctor says
全都告诉我
about your uterine climate.
好吧 还有那个
Oh, and also that.
我和Genevieve有大事要宣布
Genevieve and I have big news.
是那种别人会选择保密的事儿吗
Is this something other people would keep private?
听好了 我们要开始造人计划了
Big time! We're trying to have a baby!
哇
Oh, wow!
太棒了
That is awesome.
但是等一下 Charles 我以为你不育了
But wait, Charles, I thought you were sterile.
我特别清楚地记得你的原话是
I distinctly remember you using the phrase--
油尽灯枯
Shooting dust.
没错 谢谢你没让我说出来
Yes, thank you for not making me say it.
我确实在那场事故之后
Yeah, it's true I lost the ability
不能再生儿育女了
to procreate after the accident.
放下武器
Drop your weapons!
其实我还是不明白
Yeah, I still don't know
为什么你要冲上去先裤裆示人
why you dove in crotch first.
谢天谢地 我前妻Eleanor
Thankfully, my ex-wife, Eleanor,
在那之前一年让我做了输精管切除术
made me get a vasectomy a year before that.
以防万一 我冷冻了一些精子
As a precaution, I froze some sperm--
很多精子
a lot of sperm.
在我后面进来的人像这样
Guy going in after me was like,
哇 厉害
"Whoa, nice!"
他听起来很猥琐
Wow, he sounds like a gross dude.
是啊 我们是不是该去上班了
Yeah. Should we go into work?
没错
Yes. Great.
嘿 你不觉得
Hey, so do you think maybe
现在生孩子也许有点太急了吗
you're rushing into the whole baby thing?
我是说 你们才交往了三个月
I mean, you guys have only been dating three months.
她是我的真命天女 Jake
She's the one, Jake.
我已经不想再过花花公子的生活了
I'm done with that playboy lifestyle--
在外面待到11点 喝着汽酒
out till 11:00, drunk on sangria.
我不想要那样的生活了
I don't want that anymore.
我只想当一个爸爸
I just want to be a papa.
好吧 所以 这挺好的
Okay, yeah, so, hey, this is awesome.
你就要有个娃了
You're gonna have a baby.
我知道
I know!
而且你会成为他最好的朋友
And you're gonna be its best friend.
根据年龄差
Ah, well, based on the age diff,
大概更应该是一个有趣的叔叔兼导师
maybe more of a fun uncle/mentor.
宝宝最好的朋友
Baby's best friend.
好吧 没法协商了
All right, so... nonnegotiable.
情况这样的 Steven
Here's the deal, Steven.
我们已经抓到你盗窃了
We already got you on shoplifting.
现在我们来讨论一下你包里200张复制的信用卡
Now let's talk about the 200 cloned credit cards in your bag.
我什么都不会说
I'm not saying anything.
听着 小年轻 我们有两种方法处理这个
Look, punk, there are two ways we can do this--
简单的 或者是麻烦的
the easy way or the hard way.
告诉他麻烦的 老大
Tell him what the hard way is, boss.
首先 Steven
Well, first, Steven,
我们要填38E-J1表格
we're gonna fill out form 38E-J1,
说明你不配合
stating noncompliance.
然后把表格送到检察官那里
We send it to the DA,
但是他们会立刻处理它吗
but do they process it right away?
不 因为他们忙不过来
No, because they're overwhelmed
因为Debra休产假去了
because Debra's on maternity leave.
所以你上庭的日期在6到8周内都无法确定
So your court date won't be set for six or eight weeks,
甚至等到日期确定 你还要等一天
and even then, you're gonna have to block off the whole day,
因为他们不会给你一个确切的时间
because they don't give you a specific time.
不会的 他们给的只是时间段
No, no, it's a window.
长官
Sir...
我能跟您讲两句吗
Can I talk to you for a second?
我以为我们要吓吓他
I thought we were gonna to try to scare him.
没有比市政法院系统的真实情况更可怕的了
There's nothing scarier than the realities of the municipal court system.
现在 来吧 让我们再回去
Now, come on; let's get back in there
告诉他那个网站多糟糕
and tell him about how bad the website is.
好吧 我会交代的
Look, I'll talk.
你当然会
Of course you will.
但是我只向她交代
But I'll only talk to her.
你想向Gina交代
You want to talk to Gina?
喂 你们卖紫色裤子吗
Yeah, hi. Do you sell purple pants?
好吧 那就谢谢了
All right, well, good day, then.
这不是我想要的结果
It's not the turnout I was hoping for.
也许我应该提供点免费点心
Maybe I should've offered free strudel;
那样至少Scully会来了
then at least Scully would've come.
免费点心在哪儿
There's free strudel?
你到底从哪儿冒出来的
Where the hell did you come from?
我不太懂
I don't get it.
我觉得很震惊 竟然那么多人
I am shocked that more people
不想要来自于我们片区
wouldn't want the tutelage of our precinct's--
乃至我们市最受人尊敬的警长的教导
nay, our city's most esteemed sergeant.
你想要什么 Santiago
What do you want, Santiago?
学习宏伟壮丽的自卫术
To learn the majestic art of self-defense
师从我们市乃至我国
from our city's-nay, our country's--
拜托 快点说
Come on, man, out with it!
我要上课了
I want to start class.
好吧 其实我在申请一个
Okay, I'm applying for a mentorship program
针对上进警探的辅导项目
for up-and-coming detectives.
叫"星级导师 星级弟子"
It's called "Star Achieving Mentors,Star Achieving Mentees,"
简称"星师星弟"
Or SAM-SAM for short.
你能帮我写封推荐信吗
Would you write me a recommendation?
当然
Of course I will.
你会很棒的
You'd be great.
谢谢你 警长
Thank you, Sarge.
好了 大家
All right, everyone.
注意
Pay attention.
Santiago 我要来攻击你了
Santiago, I'm gonna come at you,
你得制服我
and you're gonna take me down.
如果你想让我写篇好推荐信的话
You better impress me if you want
你现在最好让我惊艳一下
that recommendation to be good.
我会尽力而为的 警长
I'm gonna try, Sarge.
好的 来吧
All right, here we go.
- 哦 不  - 我的鼻子
- Oh, no, no! - My nose!
我的鼻子 你打断了我的鼻子
My nose! You broke my nose!
流了好多血
Oh, there's so much blood!
非常抱歉
I'm so sorry!
拿块毛巾来
Get me a towel!
好的 好的
Okay, all right.
这就是你骗人
And that's what you get
说有免费点心的后果
for lying about free strudel.
你逃不过报应
Karma's a bitch.
滚开 Scully
Get out of here, Scully!
真相大白 正义伸张
Case closed, justice served.
Peralta最棒 哦天哪
Peralta amazing-oh, God.
不 不
Oh, no, no...
Charles Charles
Charles, Charles!
你前妻来了
Your ex-wife is here.
Eleanor
Eleanor?
那个世界毁灭者
The destroyer of worlds?
- 她为什么会来  - 可能没什么坏事儿
- Why? - Maybe it's nothing bad.
可能只是你的信寄到她家去了
Maybe some of your mail got sent to her house.
哦 天哪 我希望不是
Oh, God, I hope not.
如果是那样的话她会火冒三丈的
If that happened, she would be livid.
哦 那我们别假设是最坏情况
Oh, well, just don't assume the worst.
我就随便一说
That's all I'm saying.
那你干嘛要提信那档子事儿
Then why did you bring up the mail thing?
我不
I don't...
你好 胖墩儿
Hello, Chunk.
听说你要你的精子
Heard you want your sperm.
你得通过我这关
You gonna have to go through me.
哦 不 这比信糟糕多了
Oh, no, this is way worse than the mail thing.
什么信
What mail thing?
没事 没什么信
Nothing. There's no mail thing.
没什么信 但是那是我的精子
There's no mail thing. But it's my sperm.
你怎么发现我想要它的
How did you even find out I wanted it?
因为账户是在我名下
Because the account's under my name.
贮存机构打电话给我
Storage facility called me saying
说你想取出精子
that you were looking to make a withdrawal.
所以我先去帮你把它取出来了
So I went ahead and withdrew it for you.
我手上有你所有的精子
I have all of your sperm.
但是你又不在乎它 Eleanor
But you don't even care about it, Eleanor.
我是说 你记得吗
I mean, remember?
嘿 Charles
"Oh, hey, Charles,
我永远不会和你生孩子的
"I'll never have a baby with you
因为我不爱你
"Because I don't love you,
孩子也没办法补救
and a child's not gonna fix that!"
他刚开始用那个愚蠢的声音说话的时候
Oof, when he started doing the silly voice,
我还以为会很好笑 但是 不好笑
I thought it was gonna be more fun, but...wasn't.
我不想要你的DNA
Well, I do not want your DNA.
我想要点别的
I want something else.
我开车撞了一个蠢货
I hit some dumbass with my car.
他现在在告我
Now he's suing me.
我想让你用你的警徽
What I want is for you to use your badge
和枪吓吓他 让他放弃起诉
and your gun to intimidate him into dropping the case.
哇 那可是违法行为
Wow. That is so very illegal.
他不会干的
He's not doing that.
我不在乎
I don't care.
给你48小时 最好照我说的做
You have 48 hours to do so,
不然我就拿走你的精子
or I'm gonna take your sperm,
把它全部倒进东河里
and I'm gonna dump it into the East River.
拜托不要这么做
Please don't do that.
这样以后再也
And there will never be
不可能有一个长着呆圆脸的小Charles Boyle了
the possibility of a little pie-faced Charles Boyle, Jr.
我很自豪 我就长这样
Proud of it; it's me.
她不能这么做
She can't do that.
她能这么做吗
Can she do that?
冷静
Stay calm.
我们咨询下律师
We're gonna talk to a lawyer
获得一点专业意见
and get a professional opinion.
该死
Damn.
我不敢相信你真的签了这个条约
I can't believe you signed this contract.
那些精子是她的合法财产
The sperm is her legal possession.
这上面还写了 我引用下
It also says that, she-and I quote--
"她拥有你的尊严"
"Owns your dignity."
你就在这儿旁边签名了
You initialed right next to that.
哦不 Jake 这简直是灾难啊
Oh, no, Jake, this is a total disaster!
我这辈子都没法开心生活了
I'll never be happy in my life.
为什么你还在笑
Why are you smiling?
因为我们刚好被训练过怎么应对这种情况
Because this is exactly what we've trained for.
这是一个人质被挟持的情况
It's a hostage situation,
我们会将你的"孩子们"解救出来的
and we're gonna bring your boys home.
好的 Charles 我知道你现在已经吓坏了
All right, charles, I know that you're freaking out
你可能觉得你永远当不成爸爸了
and you think you're never gonna be a father,
但是别担心
but don't worry; there's no way
我不会让Eleanor伤害到你的
I'm gonna let Eleanor do anything to your precious...
- Boyle精华  - 呕 够了 我退出
- Boyle oil? - Ugh, all right, I'm out.
她想干啥就干啥吧
She can do what she wants.
不不不不不
No, no, no, no, no.
我们就叫它们人质吧
We'll just call them hostages.
这还差不多
All right, fine,
那就让我们行动起来吧
let's get to work.
这些是我们对Eleanor的了解
Here's what we know about Eleanor.
哦 我的婚礼
Oh, my wedding day.
我当初就应该知道这是个错误
I should've known it was a mistake
她没有说"我愿意" 而是说了"大概吧"
when she said, "I suppose," Instead of, "I do."
好了
Yowch, all right.
劫匪 Eleanor Horstweil
Hostage taker: Eleanor Horstweil.
年龄 42岁 职业 银行经理
Age 42. Occupation: bank manager.
没有犯罪前科 没有任何疾病
No priors. Clean bill of health.
现任丈夫 Hercules Thikalonos
Current husband: Hercules Thikalonos.
别把他给卷进来
Don't bring him into it.
我们俩关系还挺好的
We're actually quite close.
明白 你们在2010年离婚
Noted. You divorced in 2010.
她拿到了房子 两部车子
She got the house, both cars,
还有你从今往后的85%的工资
and 85% of your salary going forward.
这是打错了吧 对吗
That's a typo, right?
- 没打错  - 她咋拿到那么多的
- It is not. - How did she get so much?
我的律师就是Hercules
My lawyer was Hercules.
他们俩就是这样认识的
That's how they met.
这听上去也太不道德了
That seems real unethical.
再说一遍 别把Hercules牵扯进来
Again, lay off Hercules.
他还是挺好的一个人
He's quite a decent man.
好吧 听着 我们需要一些筹码
All right, look, we need some sort of bargaining chip.
你在离婚的时候
Is there anything you got
就没分到什么她特别想要的东西吗
in the divorce that she wanted?
有的 Abigail
Yes--Abigail.
我就假定
I'm gonna just assume
Abigail是个非常奇诡的东西好了
Abigail's something super weird.
不 她是我们的发型师
Nope. She was our hairdresser.
啊 好吧
Ah, okay.
如果继续再帮我们两个做头发
It was awkward for her
她会很尴尬
to see both of us,
所以她让我们做出了选择
so she made us choose.
我怎么能离开她呢
I mean, I couldn't get rid of her.
她是纽约唯一能做出这发型的造型师啊
She's the only stylist in New York that can do this.
好吧 那你觉得Eleanor还想要回Abigail吗
Right, and do you think Eleanor still wants Abigail?
你也看到她今天的发型了吧
I mean, you saw her hair today.
全都卷起来了 一点光泽也没有
It's all volume, no sheen.
好吧 或许我们能用到这个
Okay, maybe we can use this.
我们该调整成谈判模式了
Time to put on our negotiation faces.
不是特别吓人但总是控制着全局
Not too intimidating but always in control.
这个怎么样
How's this?
好像你不知道这简直完美一样
Oh, as if you don't know it's perfect.
嘿 警长
Hey, Sergeant.
你还好吗
How are you?
我孩子现在一看到我的脸
Well, my baby cries
就会被吓哭 这简直太棒了
at the sight of my face now, so that's great.
不是我说啊 她还是个孩子呢
I mean, she's a baby;
她可能会被任何东西弄哭的
she could be crying at anything.
不 她就是指着我的鼻子哭的
Nope, she pointed right at my nose
然后还吐了
and then threw up.
你想要干嘛 Santiago
What do you want, Santiago?
我只是想问问您有没有
I was just wondering if you finished
把那封推荐信写好
writing that recommendation letter.
马上就要截止了
It's due pretty soon.
我正在写呢
I'm working on it.
可能时间会长一点
It's taking a little while
因为我现在疼得要死
because it's hard to concentrate,
并不能集中精力
what with all the agony.
好吧 您还是愿意写 我很感激
Okay, well, thank you for still doing it.
我还给您带了些放松身心的姜茶 不知道能不能帮到您
If it helps, I brought you some soothing ginger tea.
它能把我鼻子和我的头骨错位的地方修好吗
Will it repair the place where my nose came off my skull?
我不知道
I don't know,
但是据说它的蒸气很治愈呢
but it's supposed to have healing vapors.
所以可以试着吸吸看
So try inhaling it?
好吧 谢谢
Oh, thank you.
疼死我了
It burns!
啊 这蒸气太刺激了
Oh! The vapors burn!
太对不起了 我马上就把它拿走
I'm sorry! I'll take it back! -
哦 天哪 我太抱歉了 我来弄点冷水
Oh, God, I'm sorry! I'll get some cold water!
不 停下
No, no, don't.
我已经怕了你了
I am petrified of you!
好的 记住了
All right, remember,
这是一次谈判
this is a negotiation.
我们不能让她知道你的渴望程度之高
We can't let her know how badly you want this.
Jake 如果她把精子销毁了怎么办
Jake, what if she destroys the sperm?
她不会这样做的 Charles
She's not gonna do that, Charles,
这样的话她就没有谈判资本了
because then she'd have no leverage.
你知道的 他们从来不会对人质开枪的
All right, you know this; they never shoot the hostage.
嘿
Hey!
你有替我威胁那个90岁的老头吗
Did you threaten that 90-year-old man for me yet?
啥 你撞的那个人都90了
What? The guy you hit was 90?
是啊 如果你们和他谈过了就会知道了
Yeah, and you would know that if you had talked to him,
所以很明显你们还没有 那就再见吧
which obviously you did not, so good-bye!
不 停下 听我说
No, no, wait, wait, look.
我们不能帮你 除非我们确认
We can't help you out until we know that
你真的拥有那些样本
you actually have the samples.
我们需要"活生生"的证据
We need proof of life.
我很乐意将其中一瓶
I'd be happy to dump
从窗户里扔下来
one of the containers out of the window.
不不不 别这样做 我求你了
No, no, no, don't do that, please!
别把我的精子扔在我们头上
Don't dumb my sperm on us!
夫人您好
Hello, ma'am.
真是一个美好的早晨啊
Top of the morning to you.
听着 如果你能让我们上楼去
All right, look, if you let us upstairs...
我们就把Abigail让给你
We'll give you Abigail.
我会给你们按铃开门的
I'll buzz you in.
这就是你怎样搞定一次谈判的
And that is how it's done.
就像从孩子手里抢糖一样轻松
Like taking candy from a baby.
为什么你要提到孩子
Why would you bring up babies right now?
- 只是俗语罢了  - 谁会干出这样的事啊
- It's a saying. - Who would do that?
问题是为什么会有人
The question is, why would someone
想和Gina谈话
want to talk to Gina?
这太没礼貌了
That's very rude.
他想找一个像她一样的平民来进行审问
It's obvious why the guy wants to talk
目的很明显啊 他在拖时间
to a civilian like her; he's stalling.
这也很没礼貌啊
That's also rude.
说不定他只是想和一个正常的人类谈话
Maybe he wants to talk to a normal person
而不是两个气势汹汹的警察
instead of two rude cops.
管他是什么想法呢
Well, whatever his reason,
我们也没有别的选择了
we have no other choice.
Gina 你来进行审问吧
Gina, take his statement.
太好啦 谢谢
Yes, thank you!
我会让这货认下
I'm gonna get this guy to admit
他甚至没有犯过的罪的
to crimes he hasn't even committed.
不要 那样问题就严重了
No, that would be a huge problem.
收到
Copy that.
我们会给你一份他的资料让你先钻研一下
We'll get you a file on him so you can study up.
不需要这样了
That won't be necessary.
我就跟着直觉走就行了
I'm gonna go with my gut.
他说了他想要Gina
He asked for Gina.
我们应该让他得到他想要的
Let's give the people what they want.
Steven Steven Steven啊
Steven, Steven, Steven...
你介意我坐下来吗
You mind if I take a seat?
坐吧
Go for it.
哦 天哪
Oh, boy.
听着 我不是一个警察
Look, I'm not a cop.
而且事实上我不怎么喜欢警察
I don't really like cops.
说真的 我觉得犯罪还有点小酷呢
Honestly, I think crime's kind of cool.
- 好吧  - 好的 你领会到我的意思了
- Okay? - Yeah, you get it.
我们还期盼着这可能行得通吗
Are we still holding out hope that this might work?
我是啊 给她一个机会试试
I am. Let's give her a shot.
我感觉我们两个真的是相通的
I feel like you and me are really bonding.
我都想豁免你了
I'm ready to give you immunity.
不 你不能那样做
No, you're not. That's not happening!
Gina你给我出来
Gina, come out of there.
不行
Negative.
这人想要
The guy wanted to talk
和一个真人交流 而不是一个警察
to a real person, not a cop.
这就是他为什么想要我的原因
That's why he asked for me.
事实上 我想让你来审问
Actually, I asked for you
是因为我们曾经在一所高中上学
because we went to high school together.
- 啥  - Steven Henderson
- What? - Steven Henderson.
我们一起上过好多课
We had a bunch of classes together.
Steven Henderson 我们还有一次在公交车上亲热来着
Steven Henderson-we made out once on the bus.
你竟然都不记得我了吗
I mean-do you not remember me?
呃
Uh...
Eleanor
Eleanor.
Jake
Jake.
Charles
Charles.
你刚刚说的是你自己的名字 伙计
Okay, you just said your own name, bud.
只剩这个了啊
It was the only one left.
好吧 听着 我们把Abigail让给了你
Okay, so we have given you Abigail.
现在该是兑现
Now it's time for you
你那部分交易的时候了
to make good on your side of the deal,
我不敢相信我要说这个
and--I can't believe I'm saying this--
给我们看看Charles的精子
show us Charles' sperm.
是我的精子
It's my sperm.
在冷柜里
It's in the freezer.
我马上就回来
I'll be right back.
你确定你知道你在做什么吗
Are you sure you know what you're doing?
Abigail是我们唯一的筹码
Abigail was our only bargaining chip.
别担心 我有一个计划的
Don't worry. I have a plan.
她一回来
As soon as she comes back in here,
我就把那个杯子从她手里抢过来
I'm gonna grab that cup right out of her hands
然后拼命地逃走
and run like hell.
你觉得这行得通吗
You think that'll work?
我不仅仅是觉得
I don't just think it will.
我确认这可能行得通
I know it might.
就在这儿了 又冷又可悲
Here it is--cold and sad.
就像你一样
Just like you.
我怎么知道这真的是Charles的
How do I know that that's really Charles'?
我得靠近点看看瓶子上的标签
I'm gonna have to read the label up close.
如果我能看一眼
If I could just take a look--
冲啊 Boyle
Go, Boyle!
你们真的觉得我那么傻吗
You really think I'm that stupid?
那不是真杯子 笨蛋们
It's called a dummy cup, dummies.
该死的 她说得没错 这是空的
Damn it. She's right; it's empty.
其实我还挺庆幸的
Oh... I'm actually kind of relieved.
我可不想看见那些东西
I did not want to see that.
你们两个惹错人了
You two are messing with the wrong woman.
现在你们要付出代价了
And now you're gonna pay for it.
等等 Eleanor Eleanor
Wait, wait! Eleanor, Eleanor!
有两个货真价实的瓶子
There are two real containers.
一个在安全的地方
One is in a safe location,
这是另一个
and this is the other one.
或者说
Or rather,
这曾经是另一个
it was the other one.
不
No!
她撕票了
She shot a hostage.
Charles 你要干什么
Charles, what are you doing?
很抱歉 Jake
I'm sorry,
但是我别无选择了
but I don't have a choice, Jake.
我要去欺负一个老神父了
I'm gonna go bully an old priest
这样我才能把我的精子拿回来
so I can get my sperms back.
他是个神父
He's a priest?
是啊 我查了一下
Yeah, I looked him up.
他是一个神父
He's a priest,
一个90岁的神父
a 90-year-old priest.
别担心 我不会伤害他的
But don't worry. I'm not gonna hurt him.
我只会随意地打一个哈欠
I'm just gonna casually yawn...
顺便露出我的枪和警徽
Thereby exposing my gun and badge.
听着Charles 你不能这样做 这是违法的
Listen, you can't do this, Charles; it's illegal.
我没别的选择了
I have to.
你也看到Eleanor对我
You saw what Eleanor did
成千上万个宝宝都做了什么
to millions of my babies.
我都听到他们尖叫了
I heard them scream!
是你在叫吧
That was you.
我们是一体的
I am them, and they are me.
你可能会进监狱的 好吗
You could go to prison, okay?
你说得对 你说得对
You're right. You're right.
我乱想什么呢
What am I thinking?
谢谢你为我着想
Thank you for looking out for me...
- 没什么  - 朋友
- Yeah. - Friend.
不 你怎么
No! What--
Charles 你这是干什么
oh, Charles, what are you doing?
别别别别别
No, no, no, no, no!
别扔钥匙 不
Not the keys, no!
噢 我早该想到这一手
Oh, I should've known.
你一般都是拥抱 不会握手的
You're a hugger, not a shaker.
这是我做过最痛苦的事了
It was the most painful thing I've ever done,
要知道我给我的三个祖父母拔过管儿呢
and I've taken three of my grandparents off life support.
怎么总是你管这些事儿啊
How are you always in charge of that?
等等 Charles 你敢上车试试
Wait, Charles, do not get in that car!
他已经上车了
He's getting in the car already.
你开车试试
Don't you drive away!
他开走了
He's driving away.
Charles
Charles!
我刚收到"星师星弟"项目发来的邮件
I just got an email from SAM-SAM.
被拒绝了
Rejected?
我从来没有被拒绝过
I've never been rejected from anything.
我也是
Me neither.
噢 你说的是拒绝还是弹出
Oops, did you say rejected or ejected?
我可是被拒绝过很多次
I've been rejected a lot.
我就不明白了
I don't understand.
我的申请写得那么好
My application was so good.
给你说 我也被弹射过
You know what? I've also been ejected.
堪萨斯州托皮卡市的激流勇进
Flume ride, Topeka, Kansas.
怎么会这样
How did this happen?
我只是忘了系安全带
Just forgot to put on the belt.
一定是Jeffords
Jeffords.
聊天愉快 Ames
Good talk, Ames.
你在推荐信里说我坏话了
You wrote me a bad recommendation.
你怎么能这样呢
How could you?
- 你说什么  - 这是唯一的解释了
- Excuse me? - It's the only explanation!
你气我打伤你的脸
You're mad that I broke your face
还烫伤了你全身了
and I burned your whole body.
成熟点好么
Well, grow up!
你叫我成熟点
Grow up?
我可是有个人退休账户的人
I have a Roth IRA!
我吃全麦吐司
I eat wheat toast!
你才要成熟一点
You grow up!
你知道吗
You know what?
给你看看我发的推荐信
Here's the letter that I sent.
"Amy Santiago是我的片区
"Amy Santiago is one of the finest detectives
乃至整个纽约警署最好的警探之一"
in my precinct-nay, the entire NYPD."
看 我还用了"乃至"
Yeah, I even used the word "Nay."
你质疑我公正的的想法真是太
The idea that you would question my integrity is so--
完了 我要打喷嚏了
Uh-oh, I got to sneeze.
会很疼的
This is gonna hurt!
噢 天哪
Oh, oh, God.
嘿 Hitchcock 谢天谢地
Oh, Hitchcock, thank God!
把你自己铐在车上了
Handcuffed yourself to a car?
我也干过这事儿
Been there.
什么 不是 是Charles干的
What? No, Charles did this.
来 赶快把钥匙给我
Here, quick, hand me those keys.
这就对了
Here we go.
你怎么报答我
What will you give me for them?
认真的吗 你说想要什么吧
Seriously? What do you want?
给我一块钱买汽水
A dollar for a soda;
我的钱都湿了
mine are all wet.
好 我答应你
Yes, obviously, I'll give you that!
哈
Bam!
汽水只要七毛五 傻瓜
A soda only costs 75 cents, you fool.
待会儿见 傻瓜
See you later, sucker!
我根本不会给他那一块钱的
Didn't even give him the dollar.
我知道看起来像是我搞砸了
I know it seems like I blew it,
但是你得再给我一次机会去搞定他
but you got to give me another crack at him.
现在我知道我们美妙的过去了
Now that I'm aware of our fascinating past,
我已经准备好说辞了
I have all the ammo that I need.
你如果读了Diaz给你的文件
Perhaps you would've had that ammo
也许早就知道该说什么了
if you had read the file Diaz offered you.
说得对 说得对 我的疏忽
No doubt. No doubt. Gina culpa.
好了 你还有一次机会
Okay, you get one more chance.
我不会让你们失望的
I will not let you down.
Steven Steven Steven 我有一个问题要问
Steven, Steven, Steven, I have one question.
当时篮球队里有谁看上我了
Who on the basketball team was into me?
给我说名字
I want names.
什么
What?
我们没时间陪你玩儿 Steven
We don't have time to play games, Steven.
到此为止了 我要把她拽出来
That's it. I'm pulling her.
先别 让她继续
No, no, let her keep going.
第二个问题
Question two...
长曲棍球队里又有谁看上我了
Who on the lacrosse team is into me,
他们里面哪个出落得最好
and which one them aged the best?
前方1.2公里保持直行
In 4,000 feet, stay straight.
就为了这个打断这首歌
You interrupted the song for that?
你好
Hello.
神父 我了解到
Father, I understand
你最近和Eleanor Horstweil
you were recently involved
发生了一次
in an automobile accident
机动车意外交通事故
with an Eleanor Horstweil.
哦 是的 她开上了人行道
Oh, yes, uh, she came up onto the sidewalk
把我的臀部撞骨折了
and fractured my hip.
你当时是步行
You were a pedestrian?
坐在长椅上
Are you technically a pedestrian
也算步行吗
if you're sitting on a bench?
坐在长椅上
Sitting on a bench...
好吧 我不是来告诉你要
Well, okay, I don't want to tell you
撤销对她的起诉
to drop your suit against her,
但是我有一点困了
but I sure am getting sleepy.
你说什么
Excuse me?
我要打哈欠了
Yawns a-coming.
放倒你了
I got you.
你好 我是Jake
Hi there. I'm Jake.
这是我最好的朋友Charles
This is my best friend, Charles.
他想要个孩子 就当你明白了
He's trying to have a baby. You get it.
来吧 走了
Now, come here, you.
Charles我知道你很生气
Charles, I know you're mad,
但是你还是得和我说话
but you have to talk to me.
有意思的是 背部被电击
It's funny how getting tased in the back
会伤了人的心
can break your heart
同时后背也疼得要死
and also really hurt your back.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我真的很想当一个父亲
I really wanted to be a papa,
但是你毁了这个机会
and you ruined it.
我临门一脚即将当爹时被你拦截了
You pop-blocked me.
我知道 但是我不能让你犯法
I know, but I couldn't let you break the law.
我也不会让Eleanor把你变成坏人
And I won't let Eleanor turn you into a bad person.
我还有别的选择吗
What other choice do I have?
办法总会有的Charles
There's always a choice, Charles
而且 不是只有DNA
And by the way, DNA is not the only thing
才能让人成为一个父亲
that makes somebody into a father.
我知道这不是我的事儿
I mean, not that it's any of my business,
但是我的生父就像个噩梦
but I have biological father, and he's a nightmare.
他从来不和我玩接球
He never played catch with me.
他从没有教过我骑车
He never taught me how to ride a bike.
我得从<小鬼当家>里学怎么刮胡子
I had to learn how to shave from watching "Home Alone."
有道理 这就像儿童版的<虎胆龙威>
Makes sense; it's like "Die Hard" For kids.
而且 你真的想让事情这么发展吗
Plus, is this how you really want it to go?
让Eleanor掌控你的生活
Eleanor controlling your life,
毁了你的前途
ruining your career?
那我该怎么办
So what do I do?
说实话 我也不知道
Honestly, I don't know.
但是我可以确定你会成为一个好父亲的
But I do know that you're gonna be a great dad
不管有没有你的
with or without your--
- Boyle精华  - 不 我是不会说出这个词的
- Boyle oil. - Nope, not gonna say it.
但你肯定会当上父亲的
But you will.
离Eleanor说的期限还有时间
There's still time left on Eleanor's deadline.
我要开门了
I'm gonna unlock this door.
想做什么就做吧
You do what you got to do.
那看起来像是不好的兆头
That seems like a bad sign.
嘿 Santiago
Hey, Santiago,
你知道为什么你没进星师星弟吗
you know why you didn't get into SAM-SAM?
也许是因为我的自荐信
Probably because I used
用了现代板式
a modern format on my cover letter
邮箱地址排版在家庭住址上面
that put my email above my home address.
干嘛要冒这个风险呢
Why take such a risk?
不 是我把推荐信
No, I sent the recommendation letter
送错了地方
to the wrong place.
我以为你是申请导师
I thought you were applying
而不是学员
to be a mentor, not a mentee.
你认为我想当星师 而不是星弟
You thought I wanted to be a SAM, not a SAM?
你疯了吗
Are you insane?
可是你应该成为一个星师
Well, you should be a SAM.
不 我应该是星弟
No, I should be a SAM.
我们别用简称了
We got to start saying something other than SAM
一会儿就弄糊涂了
because we are barreling toward a misunderstanding.
Amy 你已经可以辅导别人了
Amy, you are ready to be teaching others.
我打了个电话
I made a call;
你可以去当导师了
you're going to be a mentor.
哦 天哪
Oh, my God...
警长 我对我质疑你公正的行为
Sergeant, I'm so sorry
表示抱歉
for ever questioning your integrity.
真是太感谢了
Thank you so much--
别过来 往后站一点
No, no, no, stand back.
我还怕着你呢
Look, I'm still very scared of you.
好消息 我让Steven招了
Good news. I got Steven to talk.
Diaz 太棒了 你怎么做到的
Diaz, fantastic. How did you do it?
你是不是最终还是让他看了市政法院的网站
Did you finally show him the municipal court website
还有那个不能点击的下拉菜单
and the pulldown menus you can't click on?
不 我找到了我们的共同点
No, I found something we bonded over.
她都不知道我是谁
She didn't even know who I was.
我们曾经非常要好
And we were good friends.
她叫我Gina不止一次了
On more than one occasion, she's called me Gina.
那可是她自己的名字
That's her own name.
不会吧这都可以
No, she didn't.
我们吐槽了Gina一个小时
We complained about Gina for an hour,
然后他敞开心扉
and then he opened up-gave me the name
给我说了他是为谁做事的
of the guy he works for.
我一辈子都没被这样侮辱过
I have never been so insulted in my entire life.
我不会再为你们办案子了
I'm not gonna work cases for you guys anymore.
我们也不会让你办的
We were never going to ask you to.
你刚失去了你最好的警探
You just lost your best detective.
Charles 谢天谢地 发生什么了
Charles, thank God. What happened?
- 我做到了  - 做到什么了
- I did it. - Did what?
我在这儿担惊受怕
I'm freaking out over here;
你刚刚急匆匆的走了
you stormed off.
是啊 因为我被你鼓舞了
Yeah, because I was inspired by you.
我一路跑到Eleanor家斥责了她
I ran all the way to Eleanor's house to tell her off.
你想干嘛 胖墩儿
What do you want, Chunk?
我来告诉你留着我的精子吧
To let you know you can keep my sperm.
我不需要了
I don't need it.
我恋爱了我还要做一个父亲
I'm in love and I'm going to be a dad,
你无论如何都无法阻拦我
and there's nothing you could do to stop me.
再也不见了
So good-bye forever.
哦 对了
Oh, and one more thing--
转告Hercules周日单车课程见
tell Hercules I'll see him at spin class on Sunday.
这回真再见了
Now good-bye!
- 你们感觉怎么样  - 很好
- How do you guys feel? - Great.
我们在来这儿的路上一直在找可能的捐赠者
We were looking at possible donors on the way over.
对对对 看看这个人
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Check out this guy.
我喜欢他 他是耶鲁大学的
I like him; he went to Yale.
等等 这上面写的是"耶噜"大学
Oh, wait, that says "Yeal University."
他出局了
Swipe him off.
真有意思 诶 奇怪
This is fun-oh, that's weird.
这个人看着像我爸爸
That guy kind of looks like my dad.
等等 就是我爸
Wait a minute. That is my dad.
你们可不许用他的精子
You cannot use his sperm.
再说一遍不准用
我的儿子将会是你的弟弟啦
My son would be your brother!
电波字幕组 欢迎您的加入
官方网站:www.dbfansub.com
新浪微博:@电波字幕组